We have the results of the guest survey.
我们有了顾客调查的结果.
The good news is,
好消息是,
our guests think we do a very good job.
我们的顾客认为我们干得很棒.
But we did learn more about some of their preferences.
但是我们确实了解了更多关于他们的喜好,
Like what?
好比什么?
For instance, in the newsstand.
举例, 在报刊架上.
12% of all guests think
12%的客人认为
there should be more foreign newspapers and magazines.
那儿应该有更多的外国报纸和杂志。
I certainly agree.
我非常同意.
28% would like to see more news magazines,
28%想要看到更多新闻杂志,
and fewer fashion magazines.
和少一点的时尚杂志.
26% would like to see more fashion and life style magazines,
26%想要看到更多时尚和生活方式杂志,
and less news.
和更少的新闻杂志.
I wonder who's who.
我想知道谁是谁?
Men and women.
男人和女人.
Business travelers and vacationers?
商务旅游者和度假者吗?
We can't tell from the numbers.
我们不能从数字上看出来.
14% had no opinion about the newsstand.
14%没有意见 关于报刊架.
9% think we should sell cold drinks.
9%认为我们应该出售冷饮.
7% want a newsstand on every floor.
7%想要一个报刊架 在每层楼.
And 4% don't know we have a newsstand.
4%不知道我们有个报刊架.
How can they miss it?
他们怎么能错过它呢?
They're having too good a time to notice.
他们玩的太愉快了, 以至没注意到.